<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mol Ohep on Tiam&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/mol-ohep/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mol Ohep on Tiam&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:54:33 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/mol-ohep/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of the Jakalla Map II</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mol-ohep/2025-01-31-analysis-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:54:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mol-ohep/2025-01-31-analysis-ii/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is part 3 of my mucking about with DysonLogo&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://dysonlogos.blog/maps/my-private-jakalla/&#34;&gt;My Private Jakalla&lt;/a&gt; map. I&amp;rsquo;ve figured out how I want to position the map beneath my city, Mol Ohep. Next, I want to try and figure out what rooms are in what piecewise maps and where the big factions are.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So I went ahead and divided the map into its piecewise components. We can see that they are not square and not in a grid (shout-out especially to 1L). Making this composite map must&amp;rsquo;ve been a bunch of work!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keyed Map K</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mol-ohep/2025-04-02-keyed_map_k/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:54:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mol-ohep/2025-04-02-keyed_map_k/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;K1&#34;&gt;K1. Northern Sewer Passage&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rushing waist-high wastewater flows south towards an intersection. The brick walls are green with algae and the air is warm with stink.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rushing water:&lt;/strong&gt; The noise of the water flow and echo of the PC&amp;rsquo;s movement drowns out most other noises.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sewage:&lt;/strong&gt; The wastewater is non-potable. Because it is sewage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Physical Save:&lt;/em&gt; A creature that drinks the water or enters it with open wounds must succeed on a Physical save or contract Brown Rot (ELEPHANT: link!)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of the Jakalla Map</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mol-ohep/2025-01-25-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 12:54:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mol-ohep/2025-01-25-analysis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To get started, I downloaded the composite Jakalla map (J) from Dyson&amp;rsquo;s blog (remove the size in the link to get the full-size version instead of the tiny one). I then highlighted all the waterways to see what way the water goes. Predictably, it goes to the J river. Interestingly, there are two separate but disconnected water systems: the big one that lies to the west in the J map, and the small one confined to the NE. That&amp;rsquo;s neat; it means that my players can&amp;rsquo;t just follow the water around to get everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Private Jakalla/Mol Ohep Jakalla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mol-ohep/2025-01-25-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 12:54:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mol-ohep/2025-01-25-intro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sandboxing is fun! It means that I can prep scenarios to my heart&amp;rsquo;s content and let my players loose in them, without worrying about things like &amp;ldquo;narrative structure&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;plot&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;game balance&amp;rdquo;. Since I love nothing more than making up webs of intrigue, and nothing less than figuring out how many HD of skeletons is a reasonable amount, sandbox campaigns are a platonic ideal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So the new year&amp;rsquo;s new campaign is a sandbox campaign set in &lt;code&gt;Mol Ohep&lt;/code&gt;, a big capitol on the Mollian coast. Mol Ohep is your standard intriguing capitol: densely populated, ages old,  built on former ruins of itself. Sea to the west, plains to the north, mountains to the east; PC&amp;rsquo;s in the middle of it all trying to take advantage of the upcoming mayoral election.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
